https://www.twinpine.com/privacy/

PRIVACY POLICY
Twin Pine Casino & Hotel respects the privacy of its customers and visitors. If you have any questions about the operation of our website, please write to info@twinpine.com.
Our website collects names, email addresses, and other personal information from customers and visitors only when submitted via one of our online forms, such as our subscription form, or mailing list registration form. This data is used solely by Twin Pine Casino & Hotel and is not shared, traded, or sold to third parties—unless customers or registrants opt to receive information from like-minded organizations, in which case we share only names, email addresses, and postal addresses.
Customers can edit their personal information by logging into the secured area of our site OR by sending an email to request account changes to info@twinpine.com.
Our website also collects non-personal data through the use of server-based “session variables,” which we use to achieve important site functionality, including the recognition of logged-in users and the secure passing of shopping cart information. In order to identify customers as they proceed through the check out process, our website also uses a single “cookie” (a small file stored by your browser on your hard drive); thus, online transactions require a browser that accepts “cookies.”
Our web-server also records IP addresses from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information—all for the purpose of continually improving our website and delivering personalized, custom content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web-server environments.
Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website, for which Twin Pine Casino & Hotel is not responsible.
By using our website at twinpine.com, you signify your agreement to our privacy policy as stated above. Note that this policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used.
We have taken appropriate action and implemented enhanced health and safety measures—for you, our other Guests, and Team Members. Please make sure to follow all posted instructions while visiting Twin Pine Casino & Hotel.
An inherent risk of exposure to COVID-19 exists in any public place where people are present. COVID-19 is an extremely contagious disease that can lead to severe illness and death. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, senior citizens and Guests with underlying medical conditions are especially vulnerable. By visiting Twin Pine Casino & Hotel you voluntarily assume all risks related to exposure to COVID-19.
Be Safe. We’re doing more to keep you healthy.
ABOUT US     CAREERS     MEMORABLE MOMENTS     PRIVACY     RESPONSIBLE GAMING    ACCESSIBILITY     MEDIA     CONTACT US
2020 Copyright Twin Pine Casino & Hotel. All Rights Reserved.
Website by KL DESIGN SOLUTIONS
English
Arabic Chinese (Simplified) English Filipino French German Japanese Korean Portuguese Russian Spanish Vietnamese
